http://www.theatrehouse.com/pages/privacy

HomePopular Video ResourcesBen Nye Ben Nye AllAdhesivesBloodClownCreme KitsEyes/Lips/CheeksFace PaintingFoundation Color CakeCremeMatteKits/FX WheelsLumièreNeutralizers/ConcealersPowdersSealers/RemoversShadows/HighlightsFabricSequin FabricHatsLicensed ProdsMehron MakeupWigs70's Costumes60's CostumesClearance ItemsCatalog Fabric Collection Blacklight Fringe and TrimChiffons/Mesh/SheerFabricFake FurFringeHologram/SpotlightMetallic/Foil/GlitterMotifs & ButtonsNotionsPrint FabricsRhinestonesSilk, Satin, and TaffetaSequin FabricVelvet & VelourBlacklight All BlackLightBlacklightsBlackLight ClothingBlacklight FabricsBlacklight Fringe and TrimBlacklight MakeupBlacklight PropsBlackLight Stage ProductsCostumes 20's Costumes50's Costumes60's Costumes70's Costumes80's CostumesAnimal CostumesChildren's CostumesChristmas CostumesCostume KitsEthnic CostumesFood CostumesFun CostumesHeroes/VillainsHistorical 1600-18001900Renaissance Costumes & AccessoriesJob CostumesMascotsMilitary CostumesMovies/StoriesPirate CostumesReligiousRomanScary CostumesCostume Accessories ApronsBelts, Sashes & ScarvesBloomers & PetticoatsGlovesShoes & BootsShirts, Skirts & PantsSocks & LegwearsTies, Garters, and SuspendersDance Items AppliquesCanes, Crooks, and StaffsDance CostumesFringeGlovesPerformance Night GiftsTightsTrimTutusWingsDecorations & Gifts Awards/Gifts/DecorationsBalloons/FlagsCurtainsStage PropsTablecovers & ConfettiFabric AccessoriesFeathersHats & HeadwearHoliday & ThemesMakeupStage Lighting - Bulbs - Gels - AccessoriesSpecial Effects BlackLight ItemsBlacklightsBreakawaysCandlesFire/SmokeFog, Snow, and Bubble MachinesMagicMirror Balls/MotorsSound Effects/DialogueStage ProductsStage PropsWeaponsWigsCostumes 20's Costumes50's Costumes60's Costumes70's Costumes80's CostumesAnimal & Insect CostumesChildren's CostumesChristmas CostumesCostume KitsEthnic CostumesFood CostumesFun CostumesHeroes/VillainsHistorical 1600-18001900Renaissance Costumes & AccessoriesJob CostumesMascotsMilitary CostumesMovies/StoriesPirate CostumesReligiousRomanScary CostumesProduction Collections The Addams FamilyAlice in WonderlandAnnieArsenic and Old LaceBeauty & the BeastA Christmas CarolCinderellaThe CrucibleFrozenGrinchInto the WoodsJames and the Giant PeachThe Little MermaidThe Little Shop of HorrorsA Midsummer Night's DreamOliver!Peter and the StarcatcherRadium GirlsSeussicalShrekThe Wizard of OzYou Can't Take it With You
Skip to content
Info, Deals & Goodness
Weekly email that shares theatrical information, helpful tips, deals and useful news.
Your email
Subscribe
Open to the public. 400 W. 3rd St, Covington, KY 41011. Mon-Fri 1PM-6PM. Saturday 10am-4pm.
Subscribe & Save
HomeAccessories
ApronsBeards and MustachesBelts, Sashes and ScarvesBloomers and PetticoatsCandlesCapes and RobesCollars and CuffsCurtainsEars and TailsFansFeather BoasGlassesGlovesHollywoodJewelryMask AccessoriesNosesPatrioticShirts, Skirts and PantsShoes and BootsSports and GamesSocks and LegwearTeethTies, Garters and SuspendersTutusVestsWingsCatalog
Balloons & FlagsBest SellersBirthdayBooks and VideoDance Items
Dance CostumesTightsDecorations & GiftsFeathers
Feather BoasFeather HeadpieceFeather Plumes, Quills and SpearsFeather MasksFood and DrinkGaffers Tape
Gaffers Tape Case PackGaffers TapeSpike TapeGraduation and SchoolNewest ProductsPerformance Night GiftsPrideTablecoverCostumes
Animal & Insect CostumesChildren's CostumesChristmas CostumesClownEgyptianFamous Decades
1600-180019001920's Costumes1950's Costumes1960's Costume1970's Costumes1980's CostumesHawaiianHeroes and VillainsJob CostumesMardi Gras / CarnivaleMascotsMedievalMilitary CostumesPiratePoliceReligiousRenaissanceRomanScary CostumesSteampunkStorybook CharactersUS HistoryVegas and GangsterWestern CostumesFabric
AppliquesBlacklight FabricsBlacklight Fringe and TrimBurlap and GabardineButtonsChiffonDenimFeathersFringeFake FurHologram/SpotlightLaceLaméLiningMeshMotif & ButtonsMetallic - Foil - GlitterNotionsPrint FabricsRhinstonesSequin FabricSheerSpandexSatin, Silk & TaffetaTrimUtility FabricsVelvet and VelourHats
Animal HatsBonnetsBuckram Hat FormsChildren's HatsChristmas HatsCrowns and TiarasDerby HatsEthnic HatsFedorasFez HatsHeaddressesMardi Gras HatsMilitary HatsOccupational HatsPirate HatsReligious HatsStraw HatsTop HatsMakeup
AdhesivesBen Nye Makeup
AdhesivesBloodClownCreme Kits Eyes, Lips & CheeksFace PaintingFoundationKits/FX WheelsLumièreNeutralizers/ConcealersPowdersSealers & RemoversShadows/HighlightsFace & Body PaintingGraftobianMehron CollectionProps
Animal PropsBody PropsBreakaway GlassBlacklight & Special EffectsCanes, Crooks and StaffsFake FoodInstrumentsMagicParasolsPyrotechnics - Stage PyroSmokingSound Effects - Dialogue Stage (Fake) WeaponsWands and SceptorsSeasonal
ChristmasCinco de MayoEasterGrinchHalloweenNew YearPrideSt. Patrick's DayThanksgivingShop by Show
The Addams FamilyAlice in WonderlandAnnieArsenic and Old LaceBeauty and The BeastA Christmas CarolCinderella The CrucibleFrozenGrinchInto the WoodsJames and the Giant PeachThe Little MermaidThe Little Shop of HorrorsA Midsummer Night's DreamOliver!Peter and the StarcatcherRadium GirlsSuessicalShrekThe Wizard of OzYou Can't Take it with YouStage
BlacklightFire and SmokeFog, Snow, and Bubble MachinesGaffers TapeGlow TapeMirror BallsSpike TapeStage HardwareStage Lighting, Bulbs, Gels
GelsGobosLighting and BulbsStrobe LightsStage PaintStage PropsStrobe LightsWigs
Foam HeadsHair ProductsView All WigsWig AccessoriesBiblical WigsResources
PRIVACY STATEMENT----SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.SECTION 2 - CONSENTHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@theatrehouse.com or mailing us at:Theatre House400 W. 3rd Street Covington Kentucky US 41011SECTION 3 - DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.SECTION 4 - SHOPIFYOur store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.Payment:If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted. All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICESIn general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.LinksWhen you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.SECTION 6 - SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.SECTION 7 - COOKIESHere is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not. _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc). _shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits _shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart. _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@theatrehouse.com or by mail atTheatre House[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]400 W. 3rd Street Covington Kentucky US 41011----
Sign Up
Sign up for news, updates and savings from us here at Theatre House.
100% free, Unsubscribe any time!
Same Day Shipping
If you order before 3PM EST. We ship over 98% of our instock items same day.
Open to the Public
Supporting theatre since 1955, shop online or in our retail store in Covington, KY.
Contact Theatre House
Call or text (859) 431-2414. Fax (859) 431-1837. Our location and remittance address: Theatre House400 W. 3rd St. Covington, KY 41011.
Cash, Check, Credit Cards and PO's Accepted
If there's a way to get paid, we'll probably accept it. If you are a school and need a vendor packet or W9, shoot us a note to info@theatrehouse.com.
Opens in a new window.
